AsyncTask is unlike all the other classes that we've used before.
AsyncTask 不用于 我们之前使用的所有其他类
All the other classes,
所有其他类
like activity or view, perform their work on the main thread.
比如 Activity 或 View, 在主线程中执行工作
&gt;&gt; Yeah, with AsyncTask, however,
是的 但是 AsyncTask 类的某些部分
some parts of the class are run on the main thread in the foreground.
在前台主线程的位置 运行
And other parts of the task are run on a separate thread,
那么显然 该任务的其他部分 在后台单独的
which is obviously in the background.
线程上运行
&gt;&gt; Yes, so AsyncTask deals with more than one thread.
- 是的 AsyncTask 处理多个线程
So let's walk through this together step by step.
所以 让我们 逐个浏览
AsyncTask is an abstract class.
AsyncTask 是一个抽象类
You first learned about abstract classes from the last course with Jessica when
上节课与 Jessica 学习构建 Miwok 语言应用时
you were building the Miwok language app.
你已经对抽象类 有了一定的了解
An abstract class contains some methods that are left blank for
抽象类包含一些 留空的方法
us as developers to override and provide our own implementations.
使开发商可以覆盖和 提供自己的程序
To use an AsyncTask, we'll need to make a custom subclass.
要使用 AsyncTask 我们需要创建一个自定义的子类
We'll call this one EarthquakeAsyncTask.
我们将其称之为 EarthquakeAsyncTask
The subclass is required to override the method doInBackground().
该子类需要覆盖 方法 doInBackground()
&gt;From our earlier demonstration, whatever work you want to happen in
从早期的演示中我们得知 无论在后台线程中进行何种工作
the background thread should be included in the doInBackground() method.
该工作都包括在 doInBackground() 方法中
Once you've got the earthquake data from the server,
从服务器上获取 地震数据后
you probably want to update the UI.
你可能要对 UI 进行更新
But to update the UI you must be on the main thread, not a background thread.
但是必须在主线程更新 UI 而不是后台线程
So how do you communicate between the main and background threads?
所以要使用何种方法在 主线程和后台线程之间进行通信呢?
You can override a method in AsyncTask called onPostExecute().
你可以覆盖 AsyncTask 中 名为 onPostExecute() 的方法
This method runs on the main thread which is why I highlighted it in green.
该方法在主线程上运行 这就是我用绿色对其突出显示的原因
This method will be called after the background work is done,
将在后台工作完成后 调用此方法
which is why it's called onPostExecute().
这就是它称为 onPostExecute() 的原因
If I reveal more details about the methods,
我们可以查看 doInBackground() 返回的结果
we can see that the doInBackground() method returns a result.
来了解更多有关 方法的详细信息
That result is passed in as the input to the onPostExecute() method.
该结果会传入为 onPostExecute 方法的输入
If the result of the doInBackground() method is a list of earthquakes from
如果 doInBackground() 结果 为来自服务器的地震列表
the server, then in onPostExecute() that list of data now has been migrated back
那么在 onPostExecute() 中的 数据列表现在已经迁移回主线程
to the main thread where we can update the ListView in the app to
我们可以在主线程上的 更新应用中 ListView
display the new data.
来显示新的数据
If you need to, there is also an AsyncTask method named OnPreExecut()
如果需要的话 还有一种名为 OnPreExecut() 的 AsyncTask 方法
which is called on the main thread before the background work is started,
因为后台工作开始前 该方法就被调用到主线程上
hence the name onPreExecute().
因此称为 onPreExecute()
Developers will override this method if there's something that needs to be done
在准备运行后台工作之前 开发商可以覆盖此方法
before preparing to do the background work.
来完成某些 有待完成的工作
Sometimes the background work can take a really long time.
有时候后台工作可能会 需要很长时间
Some developers may want to update the user about the progress in
一些开发商可能想要对 后台任务中的用户进度
the background task.
进行更新
For example, an app may download a photo from the Internet,
例如 应用从网上下载 图片时
it may display a progress bar in the meantime.
会显示图片下载的 进度条
Within the doInBackground() method, we can periodically call
在 doInBackground() 方法中 我们可以定期调用
the publishProgress method and pass on the new progress value.
publishProgress 方法 并传入新的进度值
Then we can override the onProgressUpdate method which occurs on
我们可以覆盖 主线程上的 onProgressUpdate 方法
the main thread, which can be used to update the UI with a new progress value,
并用新的进度值 来更新 UI
which is 72% in this case.
在本例中进度值为 72%
Let's look at the documentation for the AsyncTask class.
让我们一起来看一下 AsyncTask 类文档
We can scroll down to the methods section and
向下滚动至 方法部分
you can see that doInBackground is listed as being an abstract method.
然后你会看到 doInBackground 在抽象方法中列出
So we are required to implement this method.
所以我们需要 执行此方法
We also recognize other methods like onPreExecute(),
我们也了解其他方法 例如 onPreExecute()、
onProgressUpdate and onPostExecute.
onProgressUpdate 和 onPostExecute
These methods are not abstract, so it's not required for
这些方法都不是抽象的 所以不需要我们
us to implement these methods.
来执行
Scrolling back up, we can also find this code example of a class called
向上滚动 我们可以发现 AsyncTask 的子类
DownloadFilesTask that subclasses AsyncTask.
名为 DownloadFilesTask 类的 代码示例
We'll talk about this example in more detail later.
我们会在后面的课程中 对该示例做出更详细的介绍
But the main gist is that in the doInBackground() method, a file is
但是主要的 gist  在 doInBackground() 方法中
downloaded, which can take a long time, so it's done on a background thread.
下载文件时 可能需要很长的时间 所以应该在后台线程中下载文件
Note that the input in the doInBackground() method can be a list of
请注意 doInBackground() 方法中的 输入可以是待处理的项目列表
items to process, which in this case, is a list of files to download.
在本例中 输入为 待下载的文件列表
Progress is reported incrementally and
下载的进度会逐渐增加
we can update the screen with the percentage progress so far.
我们可以使用当前的百分比进度 来更新屏幕
After the background work is completed, we show a dialogue with how many
后台工作结束后 会显示一个对话框
bytes of information were downloaded successfully.
该对话框显示 已成功下载的字节数
Now in this quiz, I want you to fill in this table about the most common
在本次测验中 你需要在表格中填写
callback methods in AsyncTask.
在 AsyncTask 中最常用的调用方法
Describe what each method is called in your own words, then indicate whether
用自己的话来描述 每种调用方法
the method is run on the main thread or on a background thread.
然后指出该方法是在主线程上运行 还是在后台线程上运行
You can check the link below the quiz if you need help.
如果有需要 可以查阅 测验下方的链接